<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on Invest Astuces</title>
    <link>/tags/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on Invest Astuces</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A primer on French stock market orders</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/primer-on-french-stock-market-orders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2019 17:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/primer-on-french-stock-market-orders/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article discusses the French stock market and is therefore primarily intended for English speakers living in France.
When you invest in the stock market in France, there are a variety of way to purchase or sell a security on the stock exchange depending on your desired price point as well as your buying or selling strategy. Placing stock market orders usually incurs transaction costs – so if you choose an order that is not adapted to your needs, it can quickly turn into an expensive mistake!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#39;US person&#39; status: financial restrictions for American expatriates in France</title>
      <link>/blog/2019/us-person-status-financial-restrictions-american-expats/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2019/us-person-status-financial-restrictions-american-expats/</guid>
      <description>When you are an American citizen and you plan to become a resident of France, you should be aware that having the status of a &amp;ldquo;US person&amp;rdquo; can sometimes lead to unexpected consequences for your personal finances in France, particularly concerning whether (or not!) you will be able to open a bank account. It’s better to first prepare yourself to avoid some headaches and frustration &amp;hellip;

What is a &amp;ldquo;US person&amp;rdquo;?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>